Mukta Akter

Executive Summary:

Experienced Assistant Manager with a demonstrated history of working in the computer software industry. Skilled with great communication, professional business English, leadership, project management. Additionally, I partner with HR management to explore the world of people's operation.

I started my career before starting my undergrad for which I was able to gather long client facing and team management experience in various leadership positions. Currently appointed as Assistant Manager in Field Nation Support who visions towards being the No 1 high volume on-demand job platform changing the way of work.

Education

Graduate 2018 - 2020 : MBA in Human Resource Management from North South University. (CGPA: 3.62) Undergrad 2012 – 16 : BBA in Finance from Bangladesh University of Business & Technology. (CGPA: 3.79)

HSC 2009 : HSC from BCIC College, Dhaka. (GPA 3.6 Out of 5)

SSC 2007 : SSC in Rajdhani Girls' High School, Dhaka. (GPA 4.25 Out of 5)

Professional Experiences:

June 2011 – Current: **Company:** Field Nation LTD

Position: Assistant Support Manager

Details: Field Nation is a technology company that is based in US with a branch located in Dhaka. Leading a team of support coordinators for US buyers and

providers. My responsibilities are -

- Interviewing and selecting right candidates.
- > Building company policy related documents in partnership with HR administration.
- Market research and talent hunt for new positions.
- Documenting employee status in different positions of their tenure.
- Facilitate training and coaching new recruits/existing team members in accordance with the business guidelines
- Actively monitor and report on functional and operational activities of the team
- Facilitate functional and cross functional meetings to discuss possible improvements to customer service
- Ensure the best usage of resources to achieve qualitative and quantitative targets
- Assist w/customer escalations and maintain a feedback loop to address them in a timely manner
- Confronting underachievers.
- Writing and administrating performance reviews for skill improvement

Jan 2016 - April 2016: Company: Janata Bank Limited

Position: Intern

My responsibilities involved -

- Worked cash (Deposit and Bill collection).
- Annual salary report preparation.
- Foreign exchange department.

Nov 2010 – June 2011: **Company:** Legato Solutions & Services Pte Ltd

Position: Customer Relationship Executive (CRE)

My responsibilities were-

- > Providing one-stop quality Customer Service over phone to ensure positive customer experience
- Selling through inbound and outbound contacts.
- Worked for the US outbound Debt solution campaign maintaining daily SPD target.
- Client interaction, routing calls and contacts.

Feb 2010 – Nov 2010: Company: Icon Bangladesh

Position: Supervisor

Details: Icon Bangladesh is a technology company that used to international sales

campaign. I served there as a Supervisor. My responsibilities involved -

> Interviewing and Hiring best suitable candidates.

- Making training materials and providing training to team members for sales campaign.
- Worked on UK outbound phone service provider sells campaign.

Computer and soft Skills:

- MS Office (Word, Excel, Power Point, outlook)
- > Skilled Email correspondence.
- Expert in Salesforce and Zendesk.com
- Loyal and Discreet (maintain confidentiality)
- Data Mining

- Able to Build Relationships
- > Strong analytical ability & Conflict Resolution
- > Adaptable & quick learner
- Ability to work under pressure.
- Project Management

Language and Communication

- Native Bengali speaker and can write accurately.
- Top notch oral and verbal ability in English.

Personal Information

Full Name
Father's Name
Mother's Name
Mother's Name
Date of Birth
Marital Status
Nationality
Mukta Akter
Md. Afzal Hussain
Rahela Begum
5th May 1992
Single
Bangladeshi

• Religion : Islam

I hereby declare to the best of my knowledge and believe that this CV correctly described my qualifications and me. I realize that any willful misstatement described herein may result me in disqualification, if engaged.

Signature Akta .